xtorrentp2p.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Policy regulates the way in which XTorrentP2P is collecting, using, maintaining and disclosing information from users ( identified as "User") of <https://www.xtorrentp2p.com/> ( identified as “Site”). The Privacy Policy is applicable to the site as well as other services and products offered by XtorrentP2P.

**Logging**

Just like all the websites do, we track our visitors as well as the pages they access while visiting our website. The information collected includes browser type and version, information that is collected with Google Analytics. All the data regarding browser version and type is used internally only and will never be publicly shared.

**Cookies**

TorrentFreak or any other services used by TorrentFreak may store cookies on our visitors’ computers. If you don’t want to use any cookies, you can simply disable them in the browser for our website. You will still be able to access TorrentFreak the same way you did before as we don’t make use of advertising networks with tracking cookies.

**Protecting Your Information - How Does it Work**

By implementing a wide variety of security measures, we make sure that all the personal info stored is safely kept away from any third party. Both https and the latest SSL encryptions are used to ensure the security all the information you access, submit or enter.

**Is the Information Ever Disclosed to Third Parties?**

No, we will never trade, sell or transfer any of the collected information to outside parties. These outside parties do not include the trusted parties that are assisting in operating the website, conducting business and offering top services to you. Of course, they are also obliged to agree to keep the information strictly confidential under the same safety regulations. There’s also the situation when we have to share your information when compliance with the law requests it, or for protecting our rights, property or safety as well as the rights of trusted third-parties. Non-personally-identifiable information about our visitors may be provided to third parties for advertising or marketing purposes or other uses.

**3rd Party Links**

At our complete discretion, we may occasionally include and offer third party services or products on the website. Any site you will be redirected to from the third party links will come with their own independent and separate privacy policies. Therefore, we have no liability or responsibility for the activities and content offered by these linked sites. We do, however, always strive to protect the integrity of our website and encourage all users to share any feedback about these sites.

**Strictly Online Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy only applies to information that is stored and collected through the website and doesn’t refer to any offline-collected information.

 **Contact Us**

For any further questions regarding the privacy policy or any other type of information, you can contact us using the below email address:

[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
